

DANE WALL

UX/UI Designer

CONTACT



0220770872



Auckland, NZ



danebrendynwall@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/dane-wall

EDUCATION

Yoobee School of Design

Diploma in Graphic and Web Design (UX/UI) Level 5

Sept 2017 - Current

University of Otago

Majored in Marketing & Management

2009 - 2012

EXPERIENCE

Leadership

Project Management

UX Research

Agile Development

Graphic & Web Design

PROFILE



A highly motivated, professional and hard working person, who is looking to expand on current experiences, knowledge and skills within the Design Industry. With 6 years + General Management experience in Hospitality, a robust understanding of the financial areas of businesses, extensive team leadership/participant experience, a passion for problem solving, and an eagerness to continue to learn, develop and grow.

EXPERIENCE

AMP Financial Services

Feb 2018 - present

UX Analyst - Internship

Auckland, NZ

- Solving challenges of our users through applying a user centred design process
- · Reviewing analytical data to inform design decisions
- · Brainstorm user journey touch points
- · Create innovative UI designs
- · Facilitating ideation sessions to stakeholders
- UX research



- Apply user storied approach wireframes
- Collaborate with entire design team across daily stand up meetings and various project management softwares
- · Participate in and adhere to sprint goals and objectives

Talentwire Group

Oct 2018 - Feb 2019

UX Designer - Design Lead

Auckland, NZ

- Prototype design based on target audience requirements
- · Generate ideas and develop concepts
- Research Users and highlight target audience
- Collaborate with designers and developers throughout project
- · Factor in accesibility and analytical requirements

SKILLS

Team Leadership

Financial Analysis

Adobe Suite

Web Development

Prototype Software

Problem Solving

Organisational

Project Management

Communication Skills

INTERESTS

Film

Education

Exercise

Music

Reading

Travel

Socialising

Mindfulness Meditation

SOCIAL



instagram.com/danewall111



danebrendynwall@gmail.



linkedin.com/in/dane-wall

EXPERIENCE

The Hangar

Venue Manager

Auckland, NZ

- Train, develop and lead direct reports and team members
- Maintain good PR within the local community
- Recruit, onboard and induct new staff member
- Analyse weekly and monthly profit and loss reports
- generate and implement marketing strategies and promotions
- Implement customer service initiatives, order of service, product knowledge trainings and team meetings
 - Implement and manage operations throughout all areas of the business



Searle Lane Bar & Rotisserie

May 2015 - January 2017

Jan 2017 - July 2018

Site Manager

Queenstown, NZ

- Organise all entertainment for the site and ensure they are increasing profits
- Implement all promotional activity ensuring internal and external lead generation is current and relevant
- Ensure the environment within the site is well maintained by managing temperature, volume and lighting systems
- Lead others and set the example of the business
- Complete accurate weekly and monthly stock takes

TECHNICAL SKILLS



- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Indesign
- Trello

- Sketch
- **InVision**
- Atlassian
- HTML/CSS
- Wordpress
- JavaScript
- Zeplin
- Slack

REFERENCES

Robert Milne

Talentwire

021 970 933

Richard Czarniecki

Waitakere Licensing

021 341 451

Karl Olsen

Design Lead

0276457937

rob@talentwire.co.nz richardc@thetrusts.co.nz karl.olsen@acgedu.com